AMOS GICHERO

WEB DEVELOPER

Phone: (404) 519-3561 Email:

amosgichero@gmail.com GitHub:

https://github.com/gichero Linkein: https://

www.linkedin.com/in/amos-

gichero-579913a4/

Website:

www.amosgichero.com

Profile

I began my career as a software developer three years ago when I enrolled in college to study computer programming. Since graduating, I have enrolled in digitalCrafts an immersive coding bootcamp. I am passionate about technology and currently looking for opportunities in Atlanta. I have learned the following technologies in the past 3 years: Java, Filemaker, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Python, Node, Express, jQuery, React and Redux.

Experience

Web Development Projects

<u>vinylauction.com</u>: built using react, redux, node.js, express, stripe API, PostgreSQL

Smarta: built using node.js, express, handlebars,

Google and Yelp APIs, PostgreSQL

Shaw industries

2014-2017

2017

Elutriation operator

Contributed to surpassing yearly records processing recycled carpet. I was consistently recognized for punctuality and working overtime.

Crete Carriers

2012-2014

Long haul truck driver

Accumulated over 150,000 miles without incidence delivering various goods nationally. Recognized as best rookie driver in 2013 for the Marietta, Georgia terminal.

Education

DigitalCrafts coding bootcamp

Buckhead, Atlanta 2017-2017

Chattahoochee technical college

Marietta, Georgia

Associates degree computer programming 2014-2016

University of Canberra Canberra. Australia

Bachelor business management 2002-2006